driverplex.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment

Welcome to Driverplex.com, the best site on the web for up-to-date information on device drivers in the world. We, the founders of Driverplex.com are Internet users, too, so we understand how serious you are about protecting your private information – we’re serious about it, too! To help you understand our privacy policies better, we’ve chosen to explain it below in plain English. That way, you can feel comfortable that we are just as dedicated to your privacy as we are to ours.

The bottom line is that any information we collect from you remains completely private unless you give us permission to give it to another website. We do not knowingly collect private information from children, and we don’t sell your information to any other websites for any reason. That’s it in a nutshell! If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please don’t hesitate to contact us by email or at

Driverplex.com  
45961 Warm Springs Blvd Unit #5  
Fremont, CA 94539

## Information Collected

Our computers collect non-personally identifiable data (your IP address, how often you visit our site, which pages you visit, etc.) each time you visit Driverplex.com. We use this information to make the site better – easier to use and simpler.

We will only collect personally identifiable data (your name, email address, phone number, etc.) on forms YOU complete. This information might be used for promotions, specials, or to contact you when you have a question. YOU are in complete control of what personally identifiable information you give us.

## Use of Collected Information

We will never sell your information – either kind – to anyone else, including other websites or spammers. However, if we have another company help us perform some function of our website, we will give them only the information needed to perform the function, and they are prohibited from using the information in any other way.

Also, we might share your non-personally identifiable data with third party advertisers – that’s folks who want to advertise on our website in order to offer you products and services that, as a world traveler, you might like.

Finally, we may disclose personal information if required to by law or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to

  * conform to the requirements of the law,
  * comply with a legal process served on our Company or the website, and
  * protect and/or defend our Company, website, employees, and users.

## Children

Driverplex.com does not knowingly collect any information from children.

## Cookies

Cookies are a standard Internet technology, a small text file that is put on your hard drive by the server that hosts a web page. They can’t be used to gain control of your computer or to put a virus on your computer. No one else can read our cookies, and we only use them to improve the quality of our service to you. Your Internet browser was probably originally set up to accept cookies, but you can always reset it to refuse them or to ask you each time a site tries to put one on your computer. Please note, if you don’t let us install our cookie on your computer, you can still use the website, but some parts of it might not work correctly.

## Acquisition

That’s the fancy term for if we sell Driverplex.com or the Company or merge with another company. If we do, your information might be transferred to the new company.

## Security

Driverplex.com is as committed to the security of your computer system as we are to your privacy. We use various types of standard Internet security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure.

## Changes in Privacy Policy

Driverplex.com might choose to update our privacy policy occasionally. If we do, we will post a notice on the website so you can review any changes and how they might affect you. Also, please review this page from time to time to make sure you haven’t missed any such notices. By continuing to use Driverplex.com, you are agreeing to this privacy policy and any updates we make to it.
